var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "آدَمَ",
        "answer": "O Children of Adam",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "ādama",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَاؤُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their forefathers",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "ābāuhum",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "yatīhim",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْتِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "comes to them",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "tatīhim",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآثَارَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their footprints",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "waāthārahum",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَجْرٍ",
        "answer": "and a reward",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "wa-ajrin",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرًا",
        "answer": "any payment",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "ajran",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْخُذُهُمْ",
        "answer": "it will seize them",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "takhudhuhum",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَأَتَّخِذُ",
        "answer": "Should I take",
        "pcklId": "237",
        "tlit": "a-attakhidhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّخَذُوا",
        "answer": "But they have taken",
        "pcklId": "238",
        "tlit": "wa-ittakhadhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "Then behold",
        "pcklId": "251",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "252",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "253",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "and behold",
        "pcklId": "254",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "so behold",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "Then behold",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "and behold",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "258",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذًا",
        "answer": "then",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "idhan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "(is) the earth",
        "pcklId": "329",
        "tlit": "l-arḍu",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "330",
        "tlit": "l-arḍu",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "331",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرَائِكِ",
        "answer": "[the] couches",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-arāiki",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْكُلُونَ",
        "answer": "they eat",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "yakulūna",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَأْكُلُوا",
        "answer": "That they may eat",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "liyakulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْكُلُونَ",
        "answer": "they eat",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "yakulūna",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "(are) but",
        "pcklId": "414",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "(are) but",
        "pcklId": "415",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "416",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "417",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "418",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "Except",
        "pcklId": "419",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "420",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "421",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "422",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "423",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "424",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "(is) except",
        "pcklId": "425",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1039",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(to) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1040",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1041",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "to those who",
        "pcklId": "1042",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "1043",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "Who",
        "pcklId": "1044",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "The One Who",
        "pcklId": "1045",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(He) Who",
        "pcklId": "1046",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(to) the One who",
        "pcklId": "1047",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "alīmun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَةً",
        "answer": "gods",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "ālihatan",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَةً",
        "answer": "gods",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "ālihatan",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2243",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah willed ",
        "pcklId": "2244",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2245",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "(are up) to",
        "pcklId": "543",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِمُ",
        "answer": "to them",
        "pcklId": "544",
        "tlit": "ilayhimu",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمْ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "545",
        "tlit": "ilaykum",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمْ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "546",
        "tlit": "ilaykum",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "and to Whom",
        "pcklId": "547",
        "tlit": "wa-ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِمْ",
        "answer": "to them",
        "pcklId": "548",
        "tlit": "ilayhim",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "for",
        "pcklId": "549",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "550",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "551",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمْ",
        "answer": "upon you",
        "pcklId": "552",
        "tlit": "ilaykum",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "and to Him",
        "pcklId": "553",
        "tlit": "wa-ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرُهُ",
        "answer": "His Command",
        "pcklId": "203",
        "tlit": "amruhu",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِمَامٍ",
        "answer": "a Register",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "imāmin",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "424",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "they will believe",
        "pcklId": "425",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنْتُ",
        "answer": "[I] have believed",
        "pcklId": "426",
        "tlit": "āmantu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "427",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "[the] man",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنَّىٰ",
        "answer": "then how",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "fa-annā",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their people",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "ahlihim",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَّلَ",
        "answer": "(the) first",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "awwala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآيَةٌ",
        "answer": "And a Sign",
        "pcklId": "307",
        "tlit": "waāyatun",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآيَةٌ",
        "answer": "And a Sign",
        "pcklId": "308",
        "tlit": "waāyatun",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآيَةٌ",
        "answer": "And a Sign",
        "pcklId": "309",
        "tlit": "waāyatun",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةٍ",
        "answer": "a Sign",
        "pcklId": "310",
        "tlit": "āyatin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) Signs",
        "pcklId": "311",
        "tlit": "āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبَشِّرْهُ",
        "answer": "So give him glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "fabashir'hu",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَشَرٌ",
        "answer": "human beings",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "basharun",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبْصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "see",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yub'ṣirūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبْصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(could) they see",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yub'ṣirūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعَثَنَا",
        "answer": "has raised us",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "baʿathanā",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهِ",
        "answer": "after him",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "baʿdihi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْبَغِي",
        "answer": "is permitted",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "yanbaghī",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْبَغِي",
        "answer": "it is befitting",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "yanbaghī",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَلَاغُ",
        "answer": "the conveyance",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "l-balāghu",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا بَنِي",
        "answer": "O Children of Adam",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "yābanī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "(is) before you",
        "pcklId": "233",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنِ",
        "answer": "before them",
        "pcklId": "313",
        "tlit": "bayni",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٍ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "446",
        "tlit": "mubīnin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُبِينُ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "447",
        "tlit": "l-mubīnu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٍ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "448",
        "tlit": "mubīnin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٍ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "449",
        "tlit": "mubīnin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "450",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "451",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "509",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبَعَ",
        "answer": "follows",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "ittabaʿa",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبِعُوا",
        "answer": "Follow",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "ittabiʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبِعُوا",
        "answer": "Follow",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "ittabiʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِثَالِثٍ",
        "answer": "with a third",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bithālithin",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَمَرِهِ",
        "answer": "its fruit",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "thamarihi",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "اثْنَيْنِ",
        "answer": "two (Messengers)",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ith'nayni",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "جِبِلًّا",
        "answer": "a multitude",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "jibillan",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَجْدَاثِ",
        "answer": "the graves",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-ajdāthi",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُجْرِمُونَ",
        "answer": "O criminals",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "l-muj'rimūna",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "runs",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُجْزَوْنَ",
        "answer": "you will be recompensed",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "tuj'zawna",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "[We] have placed",
        "pcklId": "244",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We have made",
        "pcklId": "245",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلَنِي",
        "answer": "and placed me",
        "pcklId": "246",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalanī",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We placed",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "made",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعٌ",
        "answer": "together",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "jamīʿun",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعٌ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "jamīʿun",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنْدٍ",
        "answer": "host",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "jundin",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنْدٌ",
        "answer": "(are) hosts",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "jundun",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتٍ",
        "answer": "gardens",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "jannātin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةَ",
        "answer": "Paradise",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "l-janata",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "(of) Paradise",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهَا",
        "answer": "came to it",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "jāahā",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَاءَ",
        "answer": "And came",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "wajāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَبًّا",
        "answer": "grain",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "ḥabban",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْزُنْكَ",
        "answer": "grieve you",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "yaḥzunka",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا حَسْرَةً",
        "answer": "Alas",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yāḥasratan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْصَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We have enumerated it",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "aḥṣaynāhu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُحْضَرُونَ",
        "answer": "(will be) brought",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "muḥ'ḍarūna",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُحْضَرُونَ",
        "answer": "(will be) brought",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "muḥ'ḍarūna",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُحْضَرُونَ",
        "answer": "(who will) be brought",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "muḥ'ḍarūna",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقَّ",
        "answer": "(has) proved true",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَحِقَّ",
        "answer": "and may be proved true",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wayaḥiqqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَكِيمِ",
        "answer": "the Wise",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "l-ḥakīmi",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We carried",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ḥamalnā",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِينٍ",
        "answer": "a time",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ḥīnin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُحْيِي",
        "answer": "[We] give life",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "nuḥ'yī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْيَيْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "We give it life",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "aḥyaynāhā",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْيِي",
        "answer": "will give life",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'yī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْيِيهَا",
        "answer": "He will give them life",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'yīhā",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيًّا",
        "answer": "alive",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "ḥayyan",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَخْتِمُ",
        "answer": "We will seal",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "nakhtimu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَخْرَجْنَا",
        "answer": "and We bring forth",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "wa-akhrajnā",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَخَشِيَ",
        "answer": "and fears",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wakhashiya",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخِصِّمُونَ",
        "answer": "are disputing",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yakhiṣṣimūna",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَصِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) an opponent",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "khaṣīmun",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَخْضَرِ",
        "answer": "[the] green ",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-akhḍari",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْفِهِمْ",
        "answer": "and behind them",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "khalfihim",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْفَكُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) behind you",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "khalfakum",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَخَلَقْنَا",
        "answer": "And We created",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "wakhalaqnā",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقْنَا",
        "answer": "[We] created",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "khalaqnā",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "[We] created him",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "khalaqnāhu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْلُقَ",
        "answer": "create",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "yakhluqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَلَّاقُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Supreme Creator",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "l-khalāqu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَلْقِ",
        "answer": "the creation",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "l-khalqi",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْقَهُ",
        "answer": "his (own) creation",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "khalqahu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْقٍ",
        "answer": "creation",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "khalqin",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَامِدُونَ",
        "answer": "(were) extinguished",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "khāmidūna",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْخُلِ",
        "answer": "Enter",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "ud'khuli",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُدْرِكَ",
        "answer": "it overtakes",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tud'rika",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَّعُونَ",
        "answer": "they call for",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "yaddaʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِ",
        "answer": "besides Him",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "dūnihi",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُرِّيَّتَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their offspring",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "dhurriyyatahum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَذْقَانِ",
        "answer": "the chins",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-adhqāni",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُكِّرْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are admonished",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "dhukkir'tum",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الذِّكْرَ",
        "answer": "the Reminder",
        "pcklId": "239",
        "tlit": "l-dhik'ra",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرٌ",
        "answer": "a Reminder",
        "pcklId": "240",
        "tlit": "dhik'run",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَذَلَّلْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "And We have tamed them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wadhallalnāhā",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْا",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "yaraw",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْا",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "yaraw",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَ",
        "answer": "see",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "yara",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "674",
        "tlit": "rabbunā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "in your Lord",
        "pcklId": "675",
        "tlit": "birabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "676",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their Lord",
        "pcklId": "677",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "678",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبٍّ",
        "answer": "a Lord",
        "pcklId": "679",
        "tlit": "rabbin",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْجَعُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be returned",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "tur'jaʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْجِعُونَ",
        "answer": "will not return",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "yarjiʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْجِعُونَ",
        "answer": "they (can) return",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "yarjiʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْجِعُونَ",
        "answer": "return",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "yarjiʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْجَعُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be returned",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "tur'jaʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجُلٌ",
        "answer": "a man",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "rajulun",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْجُلُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their feet",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "arjuluhum",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنَرْجُمَنَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "surely, we will stone you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "lanarjumannakum",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْحَمُونَ",
        "answer": "receive mercy",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "tur'ḥamūna",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنَ",
        "answer": "the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmāna",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنُ",
        "answer": "the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmānu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنُ",
        "answer": "the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmānu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنُ",
        "answer": "the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmānu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَةً",
        "answer": "(by) Mercy",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "raḥmatan",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحِيمِ",
        "answer": "the Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "305",
        "tlit": "l-raḥīmi",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٍ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "306",
        "tlit": "raḥīmin",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَزَقَكُمُ",
        "answer": "(has) provided you",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "razaqakumu",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولٍ",
        "answer": "Messenger",
        "pcklId": "378",
        "tlit": "rasūlin",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلِينَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "499",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salīna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلُونَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "500",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salūna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُرْسَلُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) Messengers",
        "pcklId": "501",
        "tlit": "mur'salūna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمُرْسَلُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) surely Messengers",
        "pcklId": "502",
        "tlit": "lamur'salūna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلِينَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "503",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salīna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلُونَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "504",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salūna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْقَدِنَا",
        "answer": "our sleeping place",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "marqadinā",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْكَبُونَ",
        "answer": "they ride",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yarkabūna",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَكُوبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "they ride them",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "rakūbuhum",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَمِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(are) decomposed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ramīmun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِدْنِ",
        "answer": "intends for me",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "yurid'ni",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَادَ",
        "answer": "He intends",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "arāda",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَزْوَاجَ",
        "answer": "(in) pairs",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "l-azwāja",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَزْوَاجُهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their spouses",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "wa-azwājuhum",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْأَلُكُمْ",
        "answer": "ask (of) you",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "yasalukum",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْبَحُونَ",
        "answer": "they are floating",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yasbaḥūna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَ",
        "answer": "Glory be",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥāna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسُبْحَانَ",
        "answer": "So glory be",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "fasub'ḥāna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَبَقُوا",
        "answer": "then they (would) race",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "fa-is'tabaqū",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَابِقُ",
        "answer": "(can) outstrip",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "sābiqu",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَدًّا",
        "answer": "a barrier",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "saddan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَدًّا",
        "answer": "a barrier",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "saddan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسِرُّونَ",
        "answer": "they conceal",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yusirrūna",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْرِفُونَ",
        "answer": "transgressing",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "mus'rifūna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْعَىٰ",
        "answer": "running",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yasʿā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسْلَخُ",
        "answer": "We withdraw",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "naslakhu",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلَامٌ",
        "answer": "Peace",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "salāmun",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْمَعُونِ",
        "answer": "so listen to me",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "fa-is'maʿūni",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "246",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَوَاءٌ",
        "answer": "And it (is) same",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "wasawāon",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّجَرِ",
        "answer": "the tree",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-shajari",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَشْحُونِ",
        "answer": "laden",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-mashḥūni",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَشَارِبُ",
        "answer": "and drinks",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "wamashāribu",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانَ",
        "answer": "the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭāna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشِّعْرَ",
        "answer": "[the] poetry",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-shiʿ'ra",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُغُلٍ",
        "answer": "will be occupied",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "shughulin",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَفَاعَتُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their intercession",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "shafāʿatuhum",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْكُرُونَ",
        "answer": "they be grateful",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "yashkurūna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْكُرُونَ",
        "answer": "they give thanks",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "yashkurūna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالشَّمْسُ",
        "answer": "And the sun",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wal-shamsu",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّمْسُ",
        "answer": "the sun",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-shamsu",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَشْهَدُ",
        "answer": "and will bear witness",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "watashhadu",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَشَأْ",
        "answer": "We will",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "nasha",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "Allah willed ",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "We willed",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "nashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "We willed",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "nashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "441",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "442",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "(in) anything",
        "pcklId": "443",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "(in) anything",
        "pcklId": "444",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "a thing",
        "pcklId": "445",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "things",
        "pcklId": "446",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابَ",
        "answer": "(of the) companions",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "aṣḥāba",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابَ",
        "answer": "(the) companions",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "aṣḥāba",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَدَقَ",
        "answer": "and told (the) truth",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "waṣadaqa",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "truthful",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَرِيخَ",
        "answer": "(would be) a responder to a cry",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṣarīkha",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطٍ",
        "answer": "a Path",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭin",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a Path",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭun",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصِّرَاطَ",
        "answer": "(to find) the path",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-ṣirāṭa",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "اصْلَوْهَا",
        "answer": "Burn therein",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "iṣ'lawhā",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصُّورِ",
        "answer": "the trumpet",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-ṣūri",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَيْحَةً",
        "answer": "a shout",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ṣayḥatan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَيْحَةً",
        "answer": "a shout",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ṣayḥatan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَيْحَةً",
        "answer": "a shout",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ṣayḥatan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاضْرِبْ",
        "answer": "And set forth",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "wa-iḍ'rib",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَضَرَبَ",
        "answer": "And he sets forth",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "waḍaraba",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِضُرٍّ",
        "answer": "any harm",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "biḍurrin",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَضَلَّ",
        "answer": "he led astray",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "aḍalla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَالٍ",
        "answer": "an error",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "ḍalālin",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَالٍ",
        "answer": "an error",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "ḍalālin",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنُطْعِمُ",
        "answer": "Should we feed",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "anuṭ'ʿimu",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَطْعَمَهُ",
        "answer": "He would have fed him",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "aṭʿamahu",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَطَمَسْنَا",
        "answer": "We (would have) surely obliterated",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "laṭamasnā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَطِيعُونَ",
        "answer": "they will be able",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "yastaṭīʿūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَطَاعُوا",
        "answer": "they would have been able",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "is'taṭāʿū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَطِيعُونَ",
        "answer": "they are able",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "yastaṭīʿūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَطَيَّرْنَا",
        "answer": "[we] see an evil omen",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "taṭayyarnā",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَائِرُكُمْ",
        "answer": "Your evil omen",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ṭāirukum",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظِلَالٍ",
        "answer": "shades",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ẓilālin",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُظْلَمُ",
        "answer": "will be wronged",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "tuẓ'lamu",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُظْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) those in darkness",
        "pcklId": "314",
        "tlit": "muẓ'limūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْبُدُ",
        "answer": "I worship",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "aʿbudu",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْبُدُوا",
        "answer": "worship",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "taʿbudū",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْبُدُونِي",
        "answer": "you worship Me",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "uʿ'budūnī",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِبَادِ",
        "answer": "the servants",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "l-ʿibādi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوٌّ",
        "answer": "an enemy",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwun",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "258",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَالْعُرْجُونِ",
        "answer": "like the date stalk",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "kal-ʿur'jūni",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُعْرِضِينَ",
        "answer": "turn away",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "muʿ'riḍīna",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَزَّزْنَا",
        "answer": "so We strengthened them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "faʿazzaznā",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزِ",
        "answer": "(of) the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzi",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزِ",
        "answer": "(of) the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzi",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِظَامَ",
        "answer": "(to) the bones",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "l-ʿiẓāma",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "use reason",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "taʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "they use intellect",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "yaʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "293",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "knew",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "they know",
        "pcklId": "295",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "[We] know",
        "pcklId": "296",
        "tlit": "naʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلَّمْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We taught him",
        "pcklId": "415",
        "tlit": "ʿallamnāhu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَلِيمِ",
        "answer": "the All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "741",
        "tlit": "l-ʿalīmi",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "742",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَلِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "743",
        "tlit": "l-ʿalīmu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعْلِنُونَ",
        "answer": "they declare",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yuʿ'linūna",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُعَمِّرْهُ",
        "answer": "We grant him long life",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "nuʿammir'hu",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمِلَتْهُ",
        "answer": "made it",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "ʿamilathu",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمِلَتْ",
        "answer": "have made",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "ʿamilat",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَعْنَابٍ",
        "answer": "and grapevines",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wa-aʿnābin",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْنَاقِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their necks",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "aʿnāqihim",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْهَدْ",
        "answer": "I enjoin",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "aʿhad",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَادَ",
        "answer": "it returns",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ʿāda",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعُيُونِ",
        "answer": "the springs",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "l-ʿuyūni",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْيُنِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their eyes",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "aʿyunihim",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُغْرِقْهُمْ",
        "answer": "We could drown them",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "nugh'riq'hum",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَغْشَيْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "and We covered them",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "fa-aghshaynāhum",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفَرَ",
        "answer": "has forgiven",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "ghafara",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمَغْفِرَةٍ",
        "answer": "of forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "bimaghfiratin",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَافِلُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) heedless",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ghāfilūna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغْلَالًا",
        "answer": "iron collars",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "aghlālan",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُغْنِ",
        "answer": "will avail",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "tugh'ni",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْغَيْبِ",
        "answer": "in the unseen",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "bil-ghaybi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَفَجَّرْنَا",
        "answer": "and We caused to gush forth",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wafajjarnā",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَطَرَنِي",
        "answer": "created me",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "faṭaranī",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاكِهَةٌ",
        "answer": "(are) fruits",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fākihatun",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاكِهُونَ",
        "answer": "(in) amusement",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "fākihūna",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَكٍ",
        "answer": "an orbit",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "falakin",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفُلْكِ",
        "answer": "the ship",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-ful'ki",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفْوَاهِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their mouths",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "afwāhihim",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلَهُمْ",
        "answer": "before them",
        "pcklId": "258",
        "tlit": "qablahum",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدَّرْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We have ordained for it",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "qaddarnāhu",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِقَادِرٍ",
        "answer": "Able",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "biqādirin",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْدِيرُ",
        "answer": "(is the) Decree",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "taqdīru",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدَّمُوا",
        "answer": "they have sent before",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "qaddamū",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَدِيمِ",
        "answer": "the old",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-qadīmi",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْقُرْآنِ",
        "answer": "By the Quran",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "wal-qur'āni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُرْآنٌ",
        "answer": "and a Quran",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "waqur'ānun",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِمُسْتَقَرٍّ",
        "answer": "to a term appointed",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "limus'taqarrin",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرُونِ",
        "answer": "the generations",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-qurūni",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَرْيَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the city",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "l-qaryati",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقْصَى",
        "answer": "(the) farthest end",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "aqṣā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُقْمَحُونَ",
        "answer": "(are with) heads raised up",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "muq'maḥūna",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْقَمَرَ",
        "answer": "And the moon ",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wal-qamara",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَمَرَ",
        "answer": "the moon",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-qamara",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "and they said",
        "pcklId": "1284",
        "tlit": "faqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "1285",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "1286",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "1287",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "1288",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1289",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "It was said",
        "pcklId": "1290",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1291",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "it is said",
        "pcklId": "1292",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "it is said",
        "pcklId": "1293",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "1294",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "1295",
        "tlit": "wayaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They [will] say",
        "pcklId": "1296",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He says",
        "pcklId": "1297",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1298",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولَ",
        "answer": "He says",
        "pcklId": "1299",
        "tlit": "yaqūla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْلُ",
        "answer": "the word",
        "pcklId": "1689",
        "tlit": "l-qawlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلًا",
        "answer": "A word",
        "pcklId": "1690",
        "tlit": "qawlan",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْلُ",
        "answer": "the Word",
        "pcklId": "1691",
        "tlit": "l-qawlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their speech",
        "pcklId": "1692",
        "tlit": "qawluhum",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "401",
        "tlit": "qawman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٌ",
        "answer": "(are) a people",
        "pcklId": "402",
        "tlit": "qawmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my People",
        "pcklId": "403",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِي",
        "answer": "my people",
        "pcklId": "404",
        "tlit": "qawmī",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "405",
        "tlit": "qawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقِيمٍ",
        "answer": "Straight",
        "pcklId": "637",
        "tlit": "mus'taqīmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Straight",
        "pcklId": "638",
        "tlit": "mus'taqīmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَكْتُبُ",
        "answer": "and We record",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "wanaktubu",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرِهِمْ",
        "answer": "most of them",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "aktharihim",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْذِبُونَ",
        "answer": "lying",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "takdhibūna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَذَّبُوهُمَا",
        "answer": "but they denied both of them",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "fakadhabūhumā",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرِيمٍ",
        "answer": "noble",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "karīmin",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُكْرَمِينَ",
        "answer": "the honored ones",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "l-muk'ramīna",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْسِبُونَ",
        "answer": "earn",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "yaksibūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْفُرُونَ",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "takfurūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "479",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُلَّ",
        "answer": "and every",
        "pcklId": "263",
        "tlit": "wakulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلٌّ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "kullun",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّهَا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "kullahā",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُلٌّ",
        "answer": "but all",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "tlit": "wakullun",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "(is) of every",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "bikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "(of) all",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتُكَلِّمُنَا",
        "answer": "and will speak to Us",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "watukallimunā",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "were We",
        "pcklId": "1054",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَتْ",
        "answer": "it was",
        "pcklId": "1055",
        "tlit": "kānat",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they did",
        "pcklId": "1056",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they",
        "pcklId": "1057",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "1058",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَتْ",
        "answer": "it will be",
        "pcklId": "1059",
        "tlit": "kānat",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used (to)",
        "pcklId": "1060",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونُوا",
        "answer": "you",
        "pcklId": "1061",
        "tlit": "takūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "1062",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "1063",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "1064",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "1065",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْ",
        "answer": "Be",
        "pcklId": "1066",
        "tlit": "kun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَكُونُ",
        "answer": "and it is",
        "pcklId": "1067",
        "tlit": "fayakūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكَانَتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their places",
        "pcklId": "1388",
        "tlit": "makānatihim",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَلَيْسَ",
        "answer": "Is it not",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "awalaysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلُ",
        "answer": "(is) the night",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "al-laylu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلُ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "al-laylu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَتَاعًا",
        "answer": "and provision",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "wamatāʿan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلُنَا",
        "answer": "like us",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "mith'lunā",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلِهِ",
        "answer": "(the) likes of it",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "mith'lihi",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلَهُمْ",
        "answer": "(the) like of them",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "mith'lahum",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَلًا",
        "answer": "an example",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "mathalan",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَلًا",
        "answer": "an example",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "mathalan",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَدِينَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the city",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-madīnati",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَّةٍ",
        "answer": "time",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "marratin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمَسَخْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "surely, We (would have) transformed them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "lamasakhnāhum",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَيَمَسَّنَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "and surely will touch you",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "walayamassannakum",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُضِيًّا",
        "answer": "to proceed",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "muḍiyyan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلَكُوتُ",
        "answer": "is (the) dominion",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "malakūtu",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَالِكُونَ",
        "answer": "(are the) owners",
        "pcklId": "204",
        "tlit": "mālikūna",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتَىٰ",
        "answer": "(to) the dead",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "l-mawtā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَيْتَةُ",
        "answer": "dead",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "l-maytatu",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَامْتَازُوا",
        "answer": "But stand apart",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wa-im'tāzū",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنْبِتُ",
        "answer": "grows",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "tunbitu",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَخِيلٍ",
        "answer": "date-palms",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "nakhīlin",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتُنْذِرَ",
        "answer": "That you may warn",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "litundhira",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْذِرَ",
        "answer": "were warned",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "undhira",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَأَنْذَرْتَهُمْ",
        "answer": "whether you warn them",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "a-andhartahum",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنْذِرْهُمْ",
        "answer": "warn them",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "tundhir'hum",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنْذِرُ",
        "answer": "you (can) warn",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "tundhiru",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُنْذِرَ",
        "answer": "To warn",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "liyundhira",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "has revealed",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent down",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنَازِلَ",
        "answer": "phases",
        "pcklId": "259",
        "tlit": "manāzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْزِيلَ",
        "answer": "A revelation",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "tanzīla",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنْزِلِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) send down",
        "pcklId": "289",
        "tlit": "munzilīna",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْسِلُونَ",
        "answer": "[they] will hasten",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yansilūna",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَسِيَ",
        "answer": "and forgets",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "wanasiya",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْشَأَهَا",
        "answer": "produced them",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ansha-ahā",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْصَرُونَ",
        "answer": "be helped",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "yunṣarūna",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصْرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "to help them",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "naṣrahum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُطْفَةٍ",
        "answer": "a semen-drop",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "nuṭ'fatin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْظُرُونَ",
        "answer": "they await",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "yanẓurūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْعَامًا",
        "answer": "cattle",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "anʿāman",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُفِخَ",
        "answer": "And will be blown",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wanufikha",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "241",
        "tlit": "anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٌ",
        "answer": "a soul",
        "pcklId": "242",
        "tlit": "nafsun",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنَافِعُ",
        "answer": "(are) benefits",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "manāfiʿu",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفِقُوا",
        "answer": "Spend",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "anfiqū",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْقِذُونِ",
        "answer": "they (can) save me",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yunqidhūni",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْقَذُونَ",
        "answer": "would be saved",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yunqadhūna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُنَكِّسْهُ",
        "answer": "We reverse him",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "nunakkis'hu",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّهَارَ",
        "answer": "the day",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "l-nahāra",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّهَارِ",
        "answer": "the day",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "l-nahāri",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْتَهُوا",
        "answer": "you desist",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "tantahū",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَارًا",
        "answer": "fire",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "nāran",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُهْتَدُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) rightly guided",
        "pcklId": "310",
        "tlit": "muh'tadūna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَهْزِئُونَ",
        "answer": "mock at him",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "yastahziūna",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَكْنَا",
        "answer": "We destroyed",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "ahlaknā",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدَةً",
        "answer": "one",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "wāḥidatan",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدَةً",
        "answer": "one",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "wāḥidatan",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدَةً",
        "answer": "single",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "wāḥidatan",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوْصِيَةً",
        "answer": "(to) make a will",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "tawṣiyatan",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَدَ",
        "answer": "(had) promised",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "waʿada",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُوعَدُونَ",
        "answer": "promised",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "tūʿadūna",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَعْدُ",
        "answer": "promise",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "l-waʿdu",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُوقِدُونَ",
        "answer": "ignite",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tūqidūna",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "Fear",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَّكِئُونَ",
        "answer": "reclining",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "muttakiūna",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "before them",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hands",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) before you",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "aydīkum",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hands",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِينَا",
        "answer": "Our hands",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "aydīnā",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِيَدِهِ",
        "answer": "in Whose hand",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "biyadihi",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "So this Day",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "fal-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "this Day",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "l-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "today",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "l-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "today",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "l-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "This Day",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "al-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "36",
        "ayah": "65"
    }
]; 
export default words;